A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, RG 1, Accession 1 FA772
Rockefeller Archive Center
National Committee on United States-China Relations records, RG 1, Accession 1
1982-2014
Rockefeller Archive Center
National Committee on United States-China Relations
FA772
60.5 Cubic Feet 150 document boxes, 1 records storage box
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Scope and Contents
Record Group 1 of the National Committee on United States – China Relations records (FA772) contains records of the National Committee's events and exchanges programs, primarily for the period 1982 to 2014; conference records; and National Committee publications and reports.
Biographical / Historical
The National Committee on United States – China Relations (NCUSCR) was established in 1966 as a nonprofit educational organization with a mission to encourage mutual understanding and dialogue between citizens of the United States and China.
The National Committee came into being through the cooperative efforts of scholars and civic, religious, and business leaders who, at a time of mutual hostility between the two countries, sought to stimulate public discussion about China and the United States' relations with it by sponsoring conferences, seminars, publications, and other education and outreach programs. In 1972, the National Committee sponsored the Chinese table tennis team's historic U. S. visit. This round of "Ping Pong Diplomacy," which followed closely on Richard Nixon's visit to China in February 1972, helped pave the way for later exchanges and, eventually, for the normalization of relations with China in 1979. Building on these cultural exchanges, the National Committee came to be a primary organizer of professional and policy exchanges between the two countries (and including Hong Kong and Taiwan), in the areas of foreign affairs and international relations, economic development, governance and legal affairs, education, mass media, environmental and global issues, etc. As its role in exchanges became more prominent, the National Committee turned over some of its educational programs to the Asia Society in the late 1970s, but it continues its educational role through public education events and ongoing outreach.
Funding for the National Committee comes from the United States government (especially the Department of State), corporations, and foundations, as well as from its individual membership.
Arrangement
The records of the National Committee on United States – China Relations are divided into ten record groups, which reflect the order in which the records were received (but which are otherwise an artificial distinction). The records are sorted intellectually into series, which carry over through all record groups, but they have received little or no physical rearrangement.
RG 1 of the NCUSCR records is arranged into six series: 1 - Events; 2 - Exchanges - General; 3 - Exchanges to China; 4 - Exchanges from China; 5 - Conferences, Seminars, Workshops, and Dialogues; and 6 - Publications and Reports.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The National Committee on United States-China Relations donated its records to the Rockefeller Archive Center by deed of gift dated March 27, 2015.
- Events, 1
  Scope and Contents
  The Events series (Series 1) includes annual members programs; luncheons and dinner meetings, often honoring visiting dignitaries, or featuring foreign policy leaders or speakers from academia, government, or business; corporate or member briefings on topical issues; and biennial gala dinners and special anniversary programs. Most events were held in New York or Washington, DC, but the series includes some briefings held in Beijing, Shanghai, or Hong Kong.
  The Events files can be uneven in contents. They often include considerable detail on arrangements and planning, but sometimes contain very little on the subject matter.
  Events, Exchanges, and Conference files are dated according to the event or trip dates. These dates do not necessarily reflect the precise date range of the contents.
  - Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs Dinner, 1982 June 25 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Wu Xueqian Luncheon, 1983 September 26 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Waldorf-Astoria Hotel.
  - Zhang Wenjin Luncheon, 1983 May 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Zhao Ziyang Luncheon - Background and Planning, 1984 January 16 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Zhao Ziyang Luncheon - VIPS and Comps, 1984 January 16 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Complimentary Invitations, Corporate Tables, Ticketing, Miscellaneous and Draft Lists
  - Zhao Ziyang Luncheon - Media, 1984 January 16 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Includes press releases and clippings concerning Zhao's visit, January 10-16, 1984.
  - Zhao Ziyang Luncheon - Lists and Seating, 1984 January 16 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Zhao Ziyang Luncheon - Speeches, 1984 January 16 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Includes Zhao's collected speeches during his visit, January 10-16.
  - Zhao Ziyang Luncheon - Follow-Up, 1984 January-February (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - All-China Youth Federation Luncheon, 1984 June 22 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Beijing Pavilion, 12:15 p.m.
  - President Li Xiannian Luncheon, 1985 July 24 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - President Li Xiannian Luncheon, 1985 July 24; FA772:181; Oversized (Box OS 1, Folder 11)
    China Daily North American Edition, Special Supplement, July 22, 1985. Welcome President Li Xiannian. 20-page broadside newspaper.
  - Arms Control Lunch, 1985 November 30 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Delegation from the Institute of Contemporary International Relations of the People's Republic of China.
  - Robert D. Hormats Luncheon, 1986 February 12 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Harvard Club
  - Caio K. Koch-Weser Luncheon, 1986 April 4 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - William A. Fisher Luncheon, 1986 May 8 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Yao Yilin Luncheon, 1986 May 19 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Pierre Hotel
  - Rong Yiren Luncheon, 1986 May 20 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    World Trade Center
  - Robert Sobel Luncheon, 1986 June 18 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Executive Briefing and Luncheon AIG, 1986 September 9 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Held at American International Group (AIG)
  - Jerome A. Cohen Luncheon, 1986 September 10 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Harry Reid Luncheon, 1986 October 30 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Harvard Club. File also includes information on a luncheon -seminar with Michael D. Thomas, to be held on December 11.
  - Twentieth Anniversary Dinner (Kissinger Dinner) - Committee, 1986 November 18 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Twentieth Anniversary Dinner (Kissinger Dinner) - Complimentary Invitations, 1986 November 18 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Twentieth Anniversary Dinner (Kissinger Dinner) - Printing, 1986 November 18 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Invitations and Seating List.
  - Twentieth Anniversary Dinner (Kissinger Dinner) - Seating, 1986 November 18 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Twentieth Anniversary Dinner (Kissinger Dinner) - Speeches, 1986 November 18 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Twentieth Anniversary Dinner (Kissinger Dinner) - Waldorf-Astoria Arrangements, 1986 November 18 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Zhang Yanning Luncheon, 1986 December 19 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    At McGraw-Hill Building.
  - Arthur H. Rosen Luncheon, 1987 February 26 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    River Club. File also includes list for rescheduled Michael D. Thomas luncheon, March 10.
  - Bank of China Luncheon, 1987 March 30 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Held at American International Group (AIG).
  - William M. Kinch Luncheon, 1987 April 23 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Yang Shangkun Luncheon, 1987 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    River Club
  - Winston Lord Luncheon, 1987 May 26 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    American Express Tower
  - Charles J. Conroy Luncheon, 1987 June 25 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Ye Qing Luncheon, 1987 November 6 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Hosted with the Port Authority of New York and New Jersey.
  - Zhu Rongji and Gao Shangquan Luncheon, 1987 December 9 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Wu Xueqian Breakfast, 1988 March 8 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    Madison Hotel, Washington, DC
  - Frank Ching Luncheon, 1988 April 7 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Tian Jiyun Breakfast, 1988 May 13 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    Shearman and Sterling
  - Zhang Yanning Luncheon, 1988 May 16 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Qian Qichen Breakfast, 1988 June 3 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    Plaza Hotel
  - Barrie Wiggham Luncheon, 1988 June 9 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Chai Chengwen Luncheon, 1988 September 28 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    River Club. In honor of General Chai and delegation from Beijing Institute for International Strategic Studies.
  - Richard W. Heimlich Luncheon, 1988 September 28 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Alan D. Romberg Luncheon, 1988 October 20 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Xinhua Luncheon (American Public Diplomacy Study Group), 1988 November 4 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    Sichuan Pavilion Restaurant. Luncheon date may have been November 3.
  - Jerome A. Cohen Luncheon, 1988 November 17 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Qin Benli Lunch, 1989 February 7 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    Sichuan Pavilion Restaurant
  - Delegation of the Foreign Affairs Committee of the National People's Congress, 1989 March 6 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    File labeled: NPC "Tea Party"
  - Nicholas R. Lardy Luncheon, 1989 March 21 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Barber Conable Dinner, 1989 April 13 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Yuan Baohua Luncheon, 1989 May 8 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Corporate Luncheon with Wan Li, 1989 May 30 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    IBM, New York
  - Briefing on China, 1989 June 6 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    Harvard Club.
  - Briefing on China (Luncheon?), 1989 June 7 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    Harvard Club. Same program as on June 6.
  - John Chan Luncheon, 1989 June 16 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    Harvard Club. Chan's speech on "Hong Kong's Role in World Trade: A View of the Future" added to file.
  - Sir David Wilson - Peter Jennings Luncheon, 1989 June 19 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Mikhail Titarenko Visit, 1989 June 25-26 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    Delegation from the Institute of Far Eastern Studies of the Soviet Academy of Sciences.
  - Taiwan Delegation Breakfast, 1989 July 25 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - China Briefing (Beijing), 1989 September 14 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    Jianguo Hotel, Beijing
  - Qian Qichen Breakfast, 1989 October 3 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Hong Kong - The Next 8 Years Panel, 1989 October 11 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    Century Club
  - Human Rights and Business as Usual Seminar, 1989 October 16 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Sir David Wilson Breakfast, 1989 October 17 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Sir David Wilson Breakfast, 1989 October 17; FA772:001; Still Image (Box 146, Folder 64)
    Portrait photo.
  - How the Japanese Do Business in China Panel, 1989 November 29 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Taiwan Redux Panel, 1989 December 13 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - State Department Briefing (on China), 1989 December 16 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    At Jones, Day, Reavis & Pogue, Washington, DC
  - Dame Lydia Dunn Luncheon, 1990 January 24 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Zhu Qizhen Breakfast, 1990 January 30 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Beijing Breakfast Briefing, 1990 March 1 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Shanghai Breakfast Briefing, 1990 March 5 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    Shanghai Hilton
  - Hong Kong Breakfast Briefing, 1990 March 7 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    Hong Kong Hilton
  - Developments in the PRC, Hong Kong, and Taiwan - American Interests and Policy, Panel Discussion, 1990 March 13 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - The United States and the Future of Hong Kong, Conference, 1990 March 29-30 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    Harvard Club. File includes biographies of participants, but no program.
  - Martin C. M. Lee Breakfast, 1990 May 3 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Corporate Members' Dinner, 1990 May 9 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    Restoran Indonesia (New York)
  - Most Favored Nation Status for China Panel, 1990 May 31 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Helmut Sohmen Luncheon, 1990 June 13 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Delegation of Mayors from the PRC Luncheon - General, 1990 July 9 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    Harvard Club. Delegation of Chinese Mayors visit, July 7-26, 1990.
  - Delegation of Mayors from the PRC Dinner - American International Group (AIG) Support, 1984-1990 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    American International Group support for the July 9, 1990, dinner. File includes correspondence on AIG's contributions to the National Committee from 1984-1990.
  - Delegation of Mayors from the PRC Visit - ALCOA Company Support, 1990 July 7-26 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Bao Keming Luncheon, 1990 August 16 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    Sichuan Pavilion restaurant
  - Anson Chan Luncheon, 1990 September 14 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Li Daoyu Luncheon, 1990 October 18 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    Chinese Mission to the United Nations
  - Paul M. F. Cheng Breakfast, 1990 November 7 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Huang Ju Breakfast, 1990 November 12 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    Harvard Club. Huang Ju was vice mayor of Shanghai.
  - John Kamm Luncheon, 1990 November 16 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Gu Yongjiang Meeting, 1990 December 7 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Jiangsu Province Economic Delegation Breakfast, 1990 December 12 (Box 4, Folder 89)
    University Club
  - Beijing and Shanghai Corporate Briefings, 1991 January 4 and 15 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    Jianguo Hotel, Beijing, January 4; Shanghai Hilton, January 15. Briefing with delegation of U. S. experts on the Middle East.
  - Huang Hua Breakfast, 1991 January 17 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Huang Hua Breakfast, 1991 January 17; FA772:002; Still Image. (Box 146, Folder 91)
    Contact prints of guests at banquet table; file cabinets and storage.
  - State Economic Reform Commission and Stock Exchange Executive Council Briefing, 1991 February 6 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    Evening program at Manufacturers Hanover Trust.
  - Jonathan Spence Program, 1991 February 25 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    Harvard Club. Annual Members' Address.
  - Taiwan Activity Evening Panel, 1991 March 6 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    Harvard Club. Panel on "Growing Economic Ties between Taiwan and the Mainland."
  - Richard Williams Luncheon, 1991 April 16 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Japanese Business Activity in Hong Kong and Taiwan Panel, 1991 April 23 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Most Favored Nation Evening Panel, 1991 May 1 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    Harvard Club. Panel on "U. S. - China Relations: Sanctions, MFN, and Human Rights."
  - Most Favored Nation Evening Panel, 1991 May 1; FA772:003; Still Image (Box 146, Folder 97)
    Headshot of panelist Anthony Lewis.
  - Rong Yiren Briefing, 1991 May 9 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Rong Yiren Luncheon, 1991 May 9 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Japan Briefings Breakfast, 1991 May 16 (Box 5, Folder 100)
    Beijing-Toronto Hotel. Briefing on "The Evolving Role of Japan in Asia." Panel appears to have been repeated in Shanghai on May 22.
  - "Hong Kong International" Breakfast, 1991 May 21 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Joseph Massey Luncheon - Cancelled, 1991 July 1 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Deng Ken Luncheon, 1991 July 19 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Hong Kong Breakfast Briefing, 1991 August 9 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Ambassador Ding Mou-Shih Dinner, 1991 September 9 (Box 5, Folder 105)
    Metropolitan Club
  - Martin C. M. Lee Luncheon, 1991 November 6 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Chinese Governors' Briefing, 1991 November 14 (Box 5, Folder 107)
    Century Club. Guo Shuyan and Delegation of Provincial Leaders.
  - Joseph Massey Luncheon, 1991 December 2 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Dai Qing Luncheon, 1992 January 21 (Box 5, Folder 109)
    UN Plaza, New York
  - Dai Qing Luncheon, 1992 January 21; FA772:004; Still Image (Box 146, Folder 109)
    Snapshot of two women at lunch table.
  - Chinese University Presidents Breakfast, 1992 January 28 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Victor Fung Breakfast; The Madison Hotel, 1992 January 29 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Reception, 1992 January 29 (Box 5, Folder 112)
    Madison Hotel, Washington, DC. Reception to honor retiring chair Raymond P. Shafer and to welcome Barber B. Conable, Jr. as incoming chair.
  - Li Peng Meeting, 1992 February 1 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Li Peng Meeting, 1992 February 1; FA772:005; Still Image (Box 146, Folder 113)
    Reception line (3 images) greeting Premier Li Peng, Brasserie, NY.
  - Li Peng Meeting (Transcript), 1992 February 1 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Laura Anderson, United States Trade Representative (USTR), Luncheon, 1992 February 6 (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - Chiefs Luncheon, 1992 March 6 (Box 6, Folder 116)
    Harvard Club. Includes paper on "Tibet: Issues for Americans."
  - Wei Wenyuan and Wang Deshun Luncheon, 1992 March 9 (Box 6, Folder 117)
  - Senator Mitch McConnell Luncheon, 1992 March 30 (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - Eden Woon and Ford Hart Luncheon, 1992 April 3 (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - Zheng Bijian Breakfast, 1992 April 24 (Box 6, Folder 120)
    NCUSCR Office
  - Huang Ju Luncheon, 1992 April 29 (Box 6, Folder 121)
    Century Club. Huang Ju was mayor of Shanghai.
  - Corporate Members' Dinner, 1992 May 21 (Box 6, Folder 122)
  - James Lilley Luncheon, 1992 June 3 (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Richard Solomon Luncheon, 1992 June 11 (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - Doug Paal Luncheon, 1992 June 18 (Box 6, Folder 125)
    Nusantara restaurant
  - Lee Sands Luncheon (Postponed), 1992 June 26 (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Liu Jianfeng Luncheon, 1992 July 10 (Box 6, Folder 127)
    Harvard Club. Liu Jianfeng was governor of Hainan Province.
  - Hsu Hsin-liang Reception, 1992 July 15 (Box 6, Folder 128)
    Harvard Club. With delegation from Democratic Progressive Party in Taiwan, of which Hsu was chair.
  - Panel on Congressional Agenda for US-China Relations, 1992 July 20 (Box 6, Folder 129)
  - Beijing Briefing Breakfast, 1992 August 13 (Box 6, Folder 130)
    Jianguo Hotel, Beijing. Breakfast with David M. Lampton.
  - Qian Qichen Dinner, 1992 September 21 (Box 6, Folder 131)
    Dinner hosted by Richard Holbrooke.
  - Lee Sands Corporate Briefing Luncheon, 1992 September 25 (Box 6, Folder 132)
    Cosmos Club, Washington, DC
  - Conable and Lampton Chicago Luncheon, 1992 October 13 (Box 6, Folder 133)
    First Chicago Corporation. With Barber B. Conable, Jr., and David M. Lampton.
  - Ezra Vogel Luncheon, 1992 October 23 (Box 6, Folder 134)
  - Ira Wolff Luncheon, 1992 October 27 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - Lu Ping Luncheon, 1992 November 6 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Congressional Forum, 1992 December 4 (Box 6, Folder 137)
    ODC, Washington, DC. Forum on the Progress of Economic Reform in China.
  - Jiao Sufen and Chai Zemin Breakfast, 1992 December 10 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Richard Lugar Dinner, 1993 January 12 (Box 7, Folder 139)
    Metropolitan Club, Washington, DC. Asia Pacific Policy Meeting.
  - Environment Panel, 1993 February 26 (Box 7, Folder 140)
    Harvard Club. Development and China's Environment.
  - China's Senior Economists Luncheon, 1993 March 8 (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - Financial Services Panel, 1993 March 10 (Box 7, Folder 142)
    Century Club. Panel on China's Opening Door for Financial Services.
  - U. S. - China Dialogue Breakfast, 1993 April 10 (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Gan Ziyu Luncheon, 1993 April 16 (Box 7, Folder 144)
    New York
  - Zhang Weiguo Breakfast, 1993 April 23 (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - Liu Hongru Dinner, 1993 April 29 (Box 7, Folder 146)
  - Annual Corporate Members' Dinner, 1993 May 6 (Box 7, Folder 147)
  - Christopher F. Patten Luncheon, 1993 May 6 (Box 7, Folder 148)
    Waldorf Astoria
  - Christopher F. Patten Luncheon (Background and Planning), 1993 May 6 (Box 7, Folder 149)
  - Li Daoyu Luncheon, 1993 May 20 (Box 7, Folder 150)
  - American Center for International Leadership (ACIL), Chinese Youth Delegation Breakfast, 1993 May 26 (Box 7, Folder 151)
    NCUSCR Office. Delegation from the All-China Youth Federation.
  - Wang Daohan Luncheon, 1993 June 2 (Box 7, Folder 152)
    Business Week
  - Sidney Rittenberg and Amanda Bennett Luncheon, 1993 June 10 (Box 7, Folder 153)
  - Zheng Hongye Luncheon, 1993 June 11 (Box 7, Folder 154)
    Peking Park restaurant
  - Col. Cai Zuming and Mr. Wang Qi Visit, 1993 June (Box 7, Folder 155)
    Facilitative assistance for their visit to New York.
  - Negotiable Instruments Legislation Study Delegation, 1993 June (Box 7, Folder 156)
  - Xu Penghang Luncheon, 1993 August 24 (Box 7, Folder 157)
  - Gu Baochang Breakfast Meeting, 1993 September 14 (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Lu Ping Breakfast, 1993 September 20 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Institute for National Policy Research (INPR) Luncheon, 1993 September 29 (Box 7, Folder 160)
    Harvard Club. Program on Taiwan's Role in the World.
  - Donald Keyser Evening Program, 1993 October 27 (Box 8, Folder 161)
  - Mikhail Titarenko Luncheon, 1993 November 2 (Box 8, Folder 162)
  - John Kamm Evening Program, 1993 December 6 (Box 8, Folder 163)
    Century Club. Talk "On Counterrevolution and American Business in China."
  - Stanley Roth Evening Program, 1993 December 8 (Box 8, Folder 164)
  - Robert Kapp Breakfast, 1994 January 14 (Box 8, Folder 165)
  - Washington Corporate Briefing, 1994 January 20 (Box 8, Folder 166)
  - Barrie Wiggham Breakfast, 1994 February 16 (Box 8, Folder 167)
  - Ruan Chongwu Breakfast, 1994 February 17 (Box 8, Folder 168)
    Century Club. Private corporate briefing with Ruan, governor of Hainan Province.
  - Li Luye Luncheon, 1994 February 17 (Box 8, Folder 169)
    Harvard Club. Includes paper on Post-Cold War Diplomacy of China.
  - Karen Elliott House Luncheon, 1994 February 23 (Box 8, Folder 170)
  - Zhao Qizheng Dinner, 1994 March 8 (Box 8, Folder 171)
    Harvard Club. Cosponsored byContinental Grain Company. Zhao was vice mayor of Shanghai.
  - Washington Corporate Briefing, 1994 March 16 (Box 8, Folder 172)
  - Mr. Huan Guocang Evening Program, 1994 March 29 (Box 8, Folder 173)
  - Song Jian Luncheon, 1994 April 15 (Box 8, Folder 174)
    Century Club. Cosponsored by NYNEX.
  - Chen Huanyou Luncheon, 1994 April 26 (Box 8, Folder 175)
    Harvard Club. Chen was governor of Jiangsu Province.
  - New Jersey World Trade Conference; Whippany, 1994 May 18 (Box 8, Folder 176)
    Whippany, NJ
  - Military Issues Team Breakfast Programs, Beijing and Hong Kong, 1994 May 27 and June 1 (Box 8, Folder 177)
  - Bo Xilai Luncheon, 1994 June 8 (Box 9, Folder 178)
    Century Club. Bo was mayor of Dalian.
  - Bo Xilai (Dalian) Luncheon (Registration Information), 1994 June 8 (Box 9, Folder 179)
  - Li Ziliu Breakfast, 1994 June 9 (Box 9, Folder 180)
    Century Club. Li was mayor of Guangzhou. Cosponsored by International Flavors and Fragrances Inc.
  - Lunch with Taiwan Scholars re - UN, 1994 June 27 (Box 9, Folder 181)
    NCUSCR Office. To discuss Taiwan's participation in the United Nations.
  - Chicago-Area Corporate and Members' Briefing, 1994 June 29 (Box 9, Folder 182)
    Metropolitan Club, Chicago. Luncheon briefing with David Lampton.
  - Military Issues Team Briefing and Reception, 1994 July 12 (Box 9, Folder 183)
    Cosmos Club, Washington, DC. Briefing on Strategic Issues in U. S. - China Relations.
  - Military Issues Team Briefing and Reception, 1994 July 12; FA772:006; 2 Still Images (Box 146, Folder 183)
    Briefing panel, with identifications.
  - Meeting with Republic of China (ROC) Group for the United Nations, 1994 September 21 (Box 9, Folder 184)
  - Lu Yucheng Luncheon, 1994 September 27 (Box 9, Folder 185)
    Century Club. Yu was vice mayor of Beijing.
  - China National School of Administration Luncheon, 1994 October 13 (Box 9, Folder 186)
    Chiam restaurant.
  - Hong Kong - USA '94 - Brochures and Printed Materials, 1994 October 17-18 (Box 9, Folder 187)